<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" media="screen" href="/~d/styles/rss2full.xsl"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" media="screen" href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~d/styles/itemcontent.css"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:feedburner="http://rssnamespace.org/feedburner/ext/1.0" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>CocoaDevBlog</title>
        <link>http://cocoadevblog.com</link>
        <description />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 13:07:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
        <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
        <!--Theme by MyThemeShop.com-->
        <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/CocoaDevBlog" />
        <feedburner:info uri="cocoadevblog" />
        <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="hub" href="http://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/" />
        <item>
            <title>How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On 7.1.2</title>
            <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~3/hnUTMw7kU4A/iphone-4s-on-7-1-2</link>
            <comments>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-2#comments</comments>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator>
                <![CDATA[Oscar Delben]]>
            </dc:creator>
            <category>
                <![CDATA[Jailbreak]]>
            </category>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/iphone4s/?p=6</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[<p>A Chinese group called Team Pangu have finally introduced their new application, which has been able to let people enjoy an untethered process when jailbreaking. It was going well until Apple released the latest IOS; many people were stuck after upgrading their devices. When you upgrade to a new IOS, you kind of lose your previous tweaks and you have to wait for an updated tool. While we were waiting for many developer teams to release something for it, Pangu stunned us with their release. At first it was in Chinese and did not have built-in Cydia. A few days </p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-2">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On 7.1.2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p>
]]>
            </description>
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[<p><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-215" src="http://cocoadevblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/712.png" alt="712" width="200" height="259" />A Chinese group called Team Pangu have finally introduced their new application, which has been able to let people enjoy an untethered process when jailbreaking.</p><p>It was going well until Apple released the latest IOS; <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7-1">many people were stuck</a> after upgrading their devices. When you upgrade to a new IOS, you kind of lose your previous tweaks and you have to wait for <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak">an updated tool.</a></p><p>While we were waiting for many developer teams to release something for it, Pangu stunned us with their release. At first it was in Chinese and did not have built-in Cydia. A few days later, they released a revised version in English which got Cydia included.</p><p><strong>Getting Started</strong></p><p>Before you use it to do an iPhone 4S 7.1.2 jailbreak, there are some steps required that you have to follow:</p><p>&#8211; Download the latest version of Pangu. (<a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/pangu7">all are listed here</a>)<br />
&#8211; Disable the passcode option, as it may not work if it is enabled.</p><p>(Settings &gt; General &gt; Passcode Lock: off)</p><p>&#8211; Disable FindMyPhone (Settings &gt; iCloud &gt; FindMyPhone)<br />
&#8211; Turn on the Airplane Mode.<br />
&#8211; Backup with iTunes or iCloud before starting, as there&#8217;s no harm in playing it safe.<br />
&#8211; Update your iTunes.<br />
&#8211; Get your USB cable ready.</p><p>Now let’s see how it works:</p><p>&#8211; Connect your device to your PC with an USB.<br />
&#8211; Install the software that you downloaded earlier, right click the .exe file and choose “Run as Administrator”.<br />
&#8211; After the installation is done, it will detect your connected device. After the detection is done and you see the model and iOS shown; go hit the “Start” button.<br />
&#8211; Click “Already Did” if you have done what we said you have to do (disabling passcode, backing up your data … etc), and the process will start.<br />
&#8211; The window will show you the steps that are left, and it will reboot many times; that’s what’s supposed to happen, it’s OK.<br />
&#8211; When it&#8217;s done, it will tell you the message “Succeeded”, and now you can see the Cydia icon on your screen.</p><p>And that&#8217;s it. Very easy right? Now the only thing that&#8217;s left is that you keep an eye out <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7">for new updates</a> by Apple, in order to keep everything working.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-2">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On 7.1.2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~4/hnUTMw7kU4A" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]>
            </content:encoded>
            <wfw:commentRss>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-2/feed</wfw:commentRss>
            <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
            <feedburner:origLink>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-2</feedburner:origLink>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On 7.1.1</title>
            <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~3/U7t1zsOIcSQ/iphone-4s-on-7-1-1</link>
            <comments>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-1#comments</comments>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 17:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator>
                <![CDATA[Oscar Delben]]>
            </dc:creator>
            <category>
                <![CDATA[Jailbreak]]>
            </category>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/iphone4s/?p=12</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[<p>Apple’s iOS now enables users to do so much more with their devices, it&#8217;s really amazing. Most users however are not satisfied at all and would stop at nothing to get the jailbreaking done in an untethered way so that they can get the most out of them. Luckily, Pangu is available, and it became a popular name very quickly. Below you can find out all that you need to know and how to use it. Compatibility This is the very first tool that was introduced that dealt with the security of this new IOS, and it did not take </p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-1">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On 7.1.1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p>
]]>
            </description>
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[<p><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-213" src="http://cocoadevblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/711.png" alt="711" width="200" height="250" />Apple’s iOS now enables users to do so much more with their devices, it&#8217;s really amazing. Most users however are not satisfied at all and would stop at nothing to get the jailbreaking done in an untethered way so that they can get the most out of them.</p><p>Luckily, Pangu is available, and it became a popular name very quickly. Below you can find out all that you need to know and how to use it.</p><p><strong>Compatibility</strong></p><p>This is the very first tool that was introduced that dealt with the security of <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7-1">this</a> new IOS, and it did not take long for a group of Chinese hackers to accomplish. It was originally compatible with Windows only and could only be run in a virtual machine on Mac. It now fully supports Mac computers as well.</p><p>Also, Cydia had to be installed separately before, but it now comes packed with this release of theirs.</p><p><strong>Getting Started</strong></p><p>You will need to disable both the FindMyPhone feature and Passcode under Settings before proceeding. The Airplane Mode should be turned on and iTunes (version 12.0.1 or later) should be on your computer. It is important to back up all data before following the steps below. (Their iPhone 4S 7.1.1 jailbreak is pretty simple, but safety should come first.)</p><p>&#8211; Download Pangu, which can be done <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/pangu7">from here</a>. Then right-click the .exe and click “Run as administrator.”</p><p>&#8211; Connect your device to the computer using an USB cable and wait for it to be detected by the software.</p><p>&#8211; Once that happened, you will notice a message telling you to click on the &#8220;Start&#8221; button. You will be asked to confirm if you have backed up your data and that you have enabled Airplane Mode. Since these have been done by you if you followed our previous steps, click “Already Did.”</p><p>The process will now start and will last for some minutes. Do not be afraid when you see it rebooting a lot while it&#8217;s on – it is normal. You should see a pop-up informing you of success if everything was done successfully.</p><p>Afterwards, the Cydia icon will appear. Cydia, the unofficial App Store, provides you access to a wide variety of tweaks to help you do much more, even those things your carrier and Apple <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak">would rather not allow you to</a>.</p><p>I suggest that you keep an eye out on <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7">this page</a>, because that&#8217;s where we mention all new updates.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-1">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On 7.1.1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~4/U7t1zsOIcSQ" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]>
            </content:encoded>
            <wfw:commentRss>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-1/feed</wfw:commentRss>
            <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
            <feedburner:origLink>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-1</feedburner:origLink>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On IOS 7.1</title>
            <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~3/zdQEurfZKRo/iphone-4s-on-ios-7-1</link>
            <comments>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7-1#comments</comments>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 11:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator>
                <![CDATA[Oscar Delben]]>
            </dc:creator>
            <category>
                <![CDATA[Jailbreak]]>
            </category>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/iphone4s/?p=30</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[<p>It has been said many times now that this is the best operating system since the release of Apple&#8217;s flagship. Most of the changes are relative to the design of the interface. The new icons were designed by the team itself, which are two and a half dimensional. The features include Airdrop, App Store, Control Center, iTunes radio and multitasking. While some of these were presented on earlier versions of the OS, it presents a totally upgraded interface, with enhanced features, graphics, and designs. Status The iPhone 4S IOS 7.1 jailbreak went live one week after the initial release, and </p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7-1">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On IOS 7.1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p>
]]>
            </description>
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[<p><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-211" src="http://cocoadevblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/71.png" alt="71" width="200" height="250" />It has been said many times now that this is the best operating system since the release of Apple&#8217;s flagship. Most of the changes are relative to the design of the interface.</p><p>The new icons were designed by the team itself, which are two and a half dimensional. The features include Airdrop, App Store, Control Center, iTunes radio and multitasking.</p><p>While some of these were presented on earlier versions of the OS, it presents a totally upgraded interface, with enhanced features, graphics, and designs.</p><p><strong>Status</strong></p><p>The iPhone 4S IOS 7.1 jailbreak went live one week after <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7">the initial release</a>, and this time not Evasi0n, but Pangu were the ones who got all the fame for it as they came up with their jailbreaking first. That being said, Pangu was a &#8220;newcomer&#8221;, as brand, but the persons behind it were well known in the community for their <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak">previous hacks and tweaks</a>.</p><p>UPDATE: 7.1.1 is live now, and a tutorial for that can <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-1">already be found</a> on our website. 7.1.2 has also been released by Apple, and several developers have been coming up with <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-2">a solution</a> for that.</p><p><strong>Stability</strong></p><p>When their older devices first hit the shelves, users were in awe, because it introduced a simple piece of technology that could complete complex tasks. However, as they released more generations and upgraded system, the complaints piled up, that is until the birth of the latest addition.</p><p>It is reported that this is the next best thing apart from when their first creation made an appearance. It was said that this OS has worked out some kinks that were shown on previous ones, which includes an upgraded Safari and Siri, which now includes a male and a female voices. iCloud, Face-time with parental controls, and additional sharing, are other updates associated with it.</p><p>It&#8217;s the introduction of a new and improved device altogether. Not only does it present new features, but it smoothed out the many issues that were present since one of the earlier operating systems, if you will. This version was designed to make navigation easier, while remaining a convenient and brilliant assistant. These are all to enhance the user’s experience by a lot.</p><p>It has been described as stable, and is in fact as exciting as their very first device that made it to the public. After this upgrade, they claim that it will really live up to its description as a miniature computer. While I personally doubt that, there definitely seem to be many improvements. I do like the fact that Siri now has male voice-overs. It just gives an extra edge to it.</p><p>While I&#8217;m still afraid of where the company&#8217;s heading to, they surely have upped their systems, meaning that they are serious about being above the competition, because they were really intervening with Apple&#8217;s business. Each quarter they lost a couple of percentages, so let&#8217;s see how they hold up next time.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7-1">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On IOS 7.1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~4/zdQEurfZKRo" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]>
            </content:encoded>
            <wfw:commentRss>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7-1/feed</wfw:commentRss>
            <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
            <feedburner:origLink>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7-1</feedburner:origLink>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On IOS 7</title>
            <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~3/NmnXFKmj1V4/iphone-4s-on-ios-7</link>
            <comments>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7#comments</comments>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 07:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator>
                <![CDATA[Oscar Delben]]>
            </dc:creator>
            <category>
                <![CDATA[Jailbreak]]>
            </category>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/iphone4s/?p=23</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[<p>This is the latest operating system designed by Apple. which was reviewed in June 2013, prior to its release which happened on September 2013. It displays an upgraded and/or redesigned interface created by Apple’s senior Vice President of Design, Jony Ive. In addition, it features a total change in functionality, and as of December, it had been installed on approximately 80% of all devices. Status Although there was no iPhone 4S IOS 7 jailbreak in the first couple of weeks, Evasi0n released it after 2 only months. Many people had been waiting for it, and the fact that it was </p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On IOS 7</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p>
]]>
            </description>
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[<p><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-209" src="http://cocoadevblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/7.png" alt="7" width="200" height="250" />This is the latest operating system designed by Apple. which was reviewed in June 2013, prior to its release which happened on September 2013. It displays an upgraded and/or redesigned interface created by Apple’s senior Vice President of Design, Jony Ive. In addition, it features a total change in functionality, and as of December, it had been installed on approximately 80% of all devices.</p><p><strong>Status</strong></p><p>Although there was no iPhone 4S IOS 7 jailbreak in the first couple of weeks, Evasi0n released it after 2 only months. Many people had been waiting for it, and the fact that it was now live was a real revolution, especially since it was the very first on the platform.</p><p>UPDATE: 7.1 has just been released, and I must say <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7-1">it looks great</a>. Alternatively, 7.1.1 is also available, and <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-1">we did get confirmation</a> from developers that a solution is available for that. The same goes for 7.1.2, which is why <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-7-1-2">we created this tutorial</a>.</p><p><strong>The Rebirth</strong></p><p>One of the main issues with this version compared the one we had before, was the questionable mapping software. It has been documented by many users that the accuracy and lack of completion, totally turned most people off, following their upgrade. The company hurriedly made a public apology on it’s website, stating that the creation of a more stable and functional one was on the way. On June 10, the Beta 1 had been released to the public, while #2 was scheduled for at the end of June,which was following by #3&#8217;s release in early July to most developers.</p><p>The 4th Beta was released in July, which had been delayed for quite a bit. At an Apple event, it was disclosed that this new update was ready for public release early in September. This OS  had many upgrades that enhanced the functionality of the device, including security, which enabled the use a pin or password, instead of a fingerprint. In late October, it was then upgraded another time and introduced animations as well as upgraded home screen options. The animation upgrade was designed to comfort those who had reportedly complained about previous animation.</p><p>So that being said, a lot of things happened. While I&#8217;m not too happy about some, all in all it&#8217;s definitely a big improvement, and I hope they keep pushing for more innovation as they&#8217;ve been lacking that for a while now. I also noticed that they increased security, making it difficult for many &#8220;underground&#8221; developers to come up with new tweaks, and most importantly, they&#8217;re having issues getting to launch Cydia again.</p><p><center><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/rT_OmTMwvZI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></center></p><p>We all know Cydia is a very big reason why we use our devices (as jailbreaking is <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak">the best thing that happened so far</a>), so I can&#8217;t really understand Apple is trying to push it out. Must be to do with either profits or are there playing things behind the scenes? Well, I guess time will tell and we&#8217;ll learn it soon enough. Until then, I&#8217;ll keep this page updated with news and so on.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On IOS 7</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~4/NmnXFKmj1V4" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]>
            </content:encoded>
            <wfw:commentRss>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7/feed</wfw:commentRss>
            <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
            <feedburner:origLink>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-7</feedburner:origLink>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On 6.1.3</title>
            <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~3/ww6rL8nh6Oc/iphone-4s-on-6-1-3</link>
            <comments>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-3#comments</comments>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 20:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator>
                <![CDATA[Oscar Delben]]>
            </dc:creator>
            <category>
                <![CDATA[Jailbreak]]>
            </category>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/iphone4s/?p=14</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[<p>P0sixspwn is a new software for jailbreaking, and is supported on both Mac OS and Windows releases. The latest version has many fixes for the iTunes 11.1+ crashing issues. Before it was released, you could have performed it untethered, but it would take you so much time and effort. First you must perform a tethered one using Redsn0w, and then change that to untethered with the p0sixspwn package on Cydia. But now, just a few clicks and you are done completely. The software is updated and has gotten many common error fixed. It now works in about 10 minutes, without </p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-3">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On 6.1.3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p>
]]>
            </description>
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[<p><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-207" src="http://cocoadevblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/6.1.3.png" alt="jailbreak iphone 4s 6.1.3" width="200" height="250" />P0sixspwn is a new software for jailbreaking, and is supported on both Mac OS and Windows releases. The latest version has many fixes for the iTunes 11.1+ crashing issues. Before it was released, you could have performed it untethered, but it would take you so much time and effort. First you must perform a tethered one using Redsn0w, and then change that to untethered with the p0sixspwn package on Cydia. But now, just a few clicks and you are done completely.</p><p>The software is updated and has gotten many common error fixed. It now works in about 10 minutes, without any struggles whatsoever.</p><p><strong>What You Need</strong></p><p>&#8211; A laptop or a computer with XP or higher, Mac 10.6+.<br />
&#8211; Updated iTunes installed.<br />
&#8211; USB cable to connect your device to your laptop / PC</p><p><strong>Getting Started</strong></p><p>Before you start with it, make sure to backup all data; just in case anything happens. Your data will be safe and sound. Now download p0sixspwn (<a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/posixspwn">all links can be found here</a>), and keep it ready for installation. Here are the next steps to take:</p><p>&#8211; Extract it&#8217;s application from the compressed file to your desktop. (Please extract to desktop or c:\ drive. Do not open it from like you would normally, but instead right click the application file and use the following option: “Run as Administrator”.<br />
&#8211; When a window appears, it will ask that you connect the device.<br />
&#8211; After connecting and being detected, it will show some information and the iOS <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6-1">that it currently runs on</a>.<br />
&#8211; Find and select the “start” button; wait till <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak">the process</a> is done. Do not disconnect anything until you are prompted to do so.<br />
&#8211; After the last reboot, the iPhone 4S 6.1.3 jailbreak should now be done. You can confirm that by finding the Cydia icon in your app list.</p><p><strong>Heads up</strong></p><p>&#8211; After starting it up from the main window, you will see the steps it needs to take as they happen on it. For example, you will see a message saying “Getting payload files from Apple”. Sometimes it fails to continue at this point, this means that there is a problem with your internet connection, be absolutely sure that it&#8217;s properly connected to the internet with a stable connection.<br />
&#8211; If you are using Windows 8; you might experience some problems. To avoid this, click on the .exe and choose properties, go to the compatibility tab and check the “Run this program in compatibility mode for” ; then select Windows 7 from the drop-down list.</p><p>If you&#8217;re looking for updates, <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6">we created this page</a>. All new things that you need to know is found on there.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-3">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On 6.1.3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~4/ww6rL8nh6Oc" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]>
            </content:encoded>
            <wfw:commentRss>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-3/feed</wfw:commentRss>
            <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
            <feedburner:origLink>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-3</feedburner:origLink>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On 6.1.2</title>
            <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~3/AzMvIhvATFk/iphone-4s-on-6-1-2</link>
            <comments>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-2#comments</comments>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 15:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator>
                <![CDATA[Oscar Delben]]>
            </dc:creator>
            <category>
                <![CDATA[Jailbreak]]>
            </category>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/iphone4s/?p=16</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[<p>P0sixspwn was initially released exclusively for MAC users, but currently, it supports Windows and will do the jailbreaking with an untethered method. It was developed by a joint team including winocm, iH8sn0w and SquiffyPwn, and the tool also offers a better compatibility than redsn0w. Before starting with it all, back up all important data. All security and pass codes should also be checked and removed. The Windows version of p0sixspwn is also more stable compared to the other version. Requirements &#8211; P0sixspwn downloaded for either Mac or Windows (depending on what you are using). &#8211; An USB cable for connecting </p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-2">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On 6.1.2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p>
]]>
            </description>
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[<p><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-205" src="http://cocoadevblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/6.1.2.png" alt="jailbreak iphone 4s 6.1.2" width="200" height="250" />P0sixspwn was initially released exclusively for MAC users, but currently, it supports Windows and will do the jailbreaking with an <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/how-to-jailbreak-iphone-44s">untethered method</a>. It was developed by a joint team including winocm, iH8sn0w and SquiffyPwn, and the tool also offers a better compatibility than redsn0w.</p><p>Before starting with it all, back up all important data. All security and pass codes should also be checked and removed. The Windows version of p0sixspwn is also more stable compared to the other version.</p><p><strong>Requirements</strong></p><p>&#8211; P0sixspwn downloaded for either Mac or Windows (depending on what you are using).<br />
&#8211; An USB cable for connecting it your PC.</p><p><strong>Steps</strong></p><p>&#8211; Download the software <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/posixspwn-download">from here</a>.<br />
&#8211; Extract it. Place the extracts somewhere where you can easily remember. In case you get an error that it is from an unidentified developer, just right-click on the app icon and choose “open”. Click “open” on the next message which will tell you that it is an application downloaded from the internet.<br />
&#8211; Use the USB to connect your device to the PC or MAC. Then go to Settings-&gt; General-&gt;Passcode lock-&gt;off. This is required so that you turn off the passcode lock. (This can be turned back on afterwards)<br />
&#8211; Select the “start” button which will appear on the screen, and follow some simple instructions.<br />
&#8211; It might need to be rebooted several times, do so if prompted.<br />
&#8211; After a number of these reboots, everything will be completed.<br />
&#8211; You will then see the Cydia App, confirming that the iPhone 4S 6.1.2 jailbreak was indeed successful. Now you can start enjoying the downloading of cool things you couldn&#8217;t access before!</p><p>if something wrong happens with your IOS, you will be <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6-1">forced to upgrade</a>, since there is no way to reinstate the one that you&#8217;re currently using. You then can&#8217;t downgrade back to the <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6">current version</a>, so be sure to have everything backed up.  Another thing to note is that during the process, you got to make sure that you don’t do anything else with it, as this might cause some interferences which in turn can cause errors.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-2">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On 6.1.2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~4/AzMvIhvATFk" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]>
            </content:encoded>
            <wfw:commentRss>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-2/feed</wfw:commentRss>
            <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
            <feedburner:origLink>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-2</feedburner:origLink>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On IOS 6.1</title>
            <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~3/IIpFQEP2XJg/iphone-4s-on-ios-6-1</link>
            <comments>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6-1#comments</comments>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 12:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator>
                <![CDATA[Oscar Delben]]>
            </dc:creator>
            <category>
                <![CDATA[Jailbreak]]>
            </category>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/iphone4s/?p=25</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[<p>This new update is the sixth major operating system out of seven designed by Apple, in 2012. The latest version of this range had been 6.1.5, which was then preceded by the 5th OS and was later succeeded by #7. It was first previewed in mid-2012, prior to it&#8217;s release to the public. The release of this upgraded system prevented the support in older versions. For example this one didn&#8217;t go live on the older devices (talking about 3G here), so that was the first time that they did do that. While on the other hand, they boosted newer models </p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6-1">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On IOS 6.1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p>
]]>
            </description>
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[<p><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-203" src="http://cocoadevblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/6.1.png" alt="jailbreak iphone 4s ios 6.1" width="200" height="250" />This new update is the sixth major operating system out of seven designed by Apple, in 2012. The latest version of this range had been 6.1.5, which was then preceded by the 5th OS and was later succeeded by #7. It was first previewed in mid-2012, prior to it&#8217;s release to the public.</p><p>The release of this upgraded system prevented the support in older versions. For example this one didn&#8217;t go live on the older devices (talking about 3G here), so that was the first time that they did do that. While on the other hand, they boosted newer models with specialized hardware, which began in late September of 2012.</p><p><strong>Status</strong></p><p>Unfortunately, when this was released, it did remove the jailbroken state. This means that all Cydia data is completely wiped out, and you&#8217;ll need to restart everything. A <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6">downgrade</a> is also not possible, because as soon as it updated, it &#8220;signed&#8221; your version, meaning you can&#8217;t change it. This is a typical move of Apple to prevent abuse of their system.</p><p>Luckily, an iPhone 4S IOS 6.1 jailbreak is already available, <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak">so there&#8217;s no need to worry at all</a>.</p><p>UPDATE: 2 new public releases! 6.1.2 turned out to <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-2">have an easy workaround</a>, no new tool was needed. 6.1.3 was <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-3">a bit more difficult</a> for developers, but they managed to create a solution for that as well!</p><p><strong>What changed</strong></p><p>The apparent upgrade enlightened many users, despite the malfunctions that it proposed upon releasing it. This newer OS seemed to enhance the already featured capabilities of the device which were limited to the date where it had been launched. Overall the function prevailed; it seemingly supersedes compared to earlier ones, by correcting some of the issues noted by users as well as the manufacturers.</p><p>Moreover, it put a jolt in the user’s smartphone experience, by actually bringing their devices to life. Even though there are many reported problems, users were reportedly able to construct business and do whatever they choose to do with it, without any type of problems. In other words, these problems did not supersede the convenience it had before.</p><p>It was designed to better the navigation and app retrieval, which just makes it more convenient, and easier to use. But, in my opinion they could&#8217;ve done so much more. Just look at Siri, where you are wondering what they&#8217;re doing with it. It really is bad, and it doesn&#8217;t understand 90% of the things that I ask her. Or check out that auto-correct feature which I&#8217;d prefer to keep on. Everytime I use Whatsapp it keeps bugging me out with incorrect fixes, which I then need to adjust myself.</p><p>It&#8217;s silly, if you keep in mind that a company that earns billions every month, can&#8217;t keep up with new changes, while other companies seemingly do just that. It&#8217;s like Apple reaches a roadblock and can&#8217;t move forward. I also can&#8217;t understand why they keep trying to stop the jailbreaking, as with every update it gets patched.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6-1">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On IOS 6.1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~4/IIpFQEP2XJg" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]>
            </content:encoded>
            <wfw:commentRss>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6-1/feed</wfw:commentRss>
            <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
            <feedburner:origLink>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6-1</feedburner:origLink>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On IOS 6</title>
            <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~3/wwCj4l-j8PU/iphone-4s-on-ios-6</link>
            <comments>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6#comments</comments>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 08:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
            <dc:creator>
                <![CDATA[Oscar Delben]]>
            </dc:creator>
            <category>
                <![CDATA[Jailbreak]]>
            </category>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/iphone4s/?p=27</guid>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[<p>Upon the release, manufacturers replaced Google Maps, with Apple maps. Subsequently, the newer one malfunctioned and often pinpointed things incorrectly. However, Google&#8217;s version were still available in the App Store for free, despite it&#8217;s previous pre-installation on earlier generations. Thus, the CEO of Apple constructed an apologetic letter on their official website, addressing the malfunctioning. Many users reportedly documented that because of the new OS that they were forced to pay higher bills, because their usage increased, and as their data plan did not cover the increase, prices rose. In January of 2013, .1 was released and it too had </p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On IOS 6</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p>
]]>
            </description>
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[<p><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-200" src="http://cocoadevblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/6.png" alt="jailbreak iphone 4s ios 6" width="200" height="250" />Upon the release, manufacturers replaced Google Maps, with Apple maps. Subsequently, the newer one malfunctioned and often pinpointed things incorrectly. However, Google&#8217;s version were still available in the App Store for free, despite it&#8217;s previous pre-installation on earlier generations.</p><p>Thus, the CEO of Apple constructed an apologetic letter on their official website, addressing the malfunctioning. Many users reportedly documented that because of the new OS that they were forced to pay higher bills, because their usage increased, and as their data plan did not cover the increase, prices rose. In January of 2013, .1 was released and it too had some reported malfunctions. Many  also complained of shortened battery life, which wasn’t present in previous versions.</p><p><strong>Status</strong></p><p>This update completely blown out the option to get it jailbroken, something that was presented in the <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak">earlier versions</a>. This means that if you had Cydia, it is now removed. The same goes for all apps as well as the tweaks that you had already configured. Even though this is annoying, someone with more experience would&#8217;ve saved their SHSH blobs so they could eventually downgraded.</p><p>If you didn&#8217;t however, then there&#8217;s no need to worry either &#8211; as an iPhone 4S IOS 6 jailbreak had been released shortly afterwards.</p><p>UPDATE: Because 6.1 got <a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6-1">released to the public</a>, you need to be more careful now as it required a new tool, the same goes for 6.1.2 (<a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-2">here</a>) and 6.1.3 (<a href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-6-1-3">here</a>).</p><p><strong>Features</strong></p><p>Despite the removal of YouTube from its pre-installed list, the OS introduced passbook and turn navigation, which we didn&#8217;t have access to before. The turn  feature includes real time traffic, 3D view, and spoken directions in some countries. Passbook is a feature that allows us to obtain documents, coupons, boarding passes, and admission tickets. It allows users to process payments and/or admission fees at places that are participating via different payment processors.</p><p>This new update also added an improved SIRI, which allows the personal assistant to make restaurant reservations, update social networks (Facebook and Twitter), as well as, launch many apps, retrieve sport info and movie reviews, if you will. This social network comes standard as always, so we can sync our contacts and events, which are accessible through integrated apps.</p><p>In addition, it also introduces sharing through other platforms such as Twitter, and Sina Weibo via bluetooth. Moreover, calendars, address books, and reminders, are fully accessible. Now that being said, I believe it truly is a decent move, but still not perfect. I keep thinking about those early days, where everything was simply mind blowing, while now it seems to be just OK, I guess.</p><p><center><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xpdjUla8o1w" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></center></p><p>It&#8217;s decent, but at the same time nothing really stands out either as of right now. Again, no progress has been shown, and in turn, we&#8217;re getting a slightly over tuned update which adds nothing more than bandwidth. So take that as you will, but I think it&#8217;ll be business as usual for us. No more good things to count on, so I&#8217;m turning my hope factor down for a bit. It&#8217;s a good thing though that we can still begin with jailbreaking, as without it, it&#8217;s hopeless.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6">How To Jailbreak iPhone 4/4S On IOS 6</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://cocoadevblog.com">CocoaDevBlog</a>.</p><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/CocoaDevBlog/~4/wwCj4l-j8PU" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]>
            </content:encoded>
            <wfw:commentRss>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6/feed</wfw:commentRss>
            <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
            <feedburner:origLink>http://cocoadevblog.com/jailbreak/iphone-4s-on-ios-6</feedburner:origLink>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
